Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - Texas
    - Odessa
      - PP Ector County, 1966-1974 (Box 180, Folder 54)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1966-1972 (Box 180, Folder 55)
    - Robstown
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966-1971 (Box 180, Folder 56)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 180, Folder 57)
      - PP Committee, 1962-1974 (Box 180, Folder 58)
      - Field Trips, 1962-1963 (Box 180, Folder 59)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1966-1970 (Box 180, Folder 60)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 180, Folder 61)
    - San Angelo
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1972 (Box 180, Folder 62)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 180, Folder 63)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1963 (Box 180, Folder 64)
      - PP Center of San Angelo, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 65)
      - PP Center
        - 1962-1974 (Box 180, Folder 66)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1961 (Box 180, Folder 67)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1955-1963 (Box 180, Folder 68)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1955-1963 (Box 180, Folder 69)
    - San Antonio
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 180, Folder 70)
        - 1977 (Box 180)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence from 1951
        - 1951-1974 (Box 180, Folder 71)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 180)
      - PP Center from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 180, Folder 72)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 180)
      - PP Center, 1970-1971 (Box 180, Folder 73)
      - PP Center, 1964-1969 (Box 181, Folder 1-3)
      - PP Center, Reports, General, 1955-1971 (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - PP Center, Reports, Members, 1964-1973 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Publicity, 1964-1969 (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - South West Foundation for Research & Education, Dr. Goldzieher, 1955-1969 (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1963 (Box 181, Folder 8)
      - International Exposition, Hemisfair, 1967-1968 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Sequin, PP Association of Guadalupe County, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Texarkana, PP Committee, 1962 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Tyler
      - PP Association of East Texas, 1961-1965 (Box 181, Folder 12)
      - Smith County PP, 1969-1971 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Victoria, PP of Victoria County, 1969-1970 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Waco
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1950
        - 1950-1973 (Box 181, Folder 15)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 181)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1952
        - 1952-1974 (Box 181, Folder 16)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 181)
      - PP from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 181, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 181)
      - PP, 1963-1967 (Box 181, Folder 18)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1966 (Box 181, Folder 19)
      - Reports, General, 1965-1970 (Box 181, Folder 20)
      - Reports, Members, 1964-1971 (Box 181, Folder 21)
      - Publicity, 1965-1968 (Box 181, Folder 22)
      - Field Trips, 1957-1963 (Box 181, Folder 23)
    - General, Field Trips, 1959-1962 (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - Southwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1966 (Box 181, Folder 25)
  - Utah
    - Anti-Poverty, 1966-1970 (Box 181, Folder 26)
    - Contacts, 1962-1972 (Box 181, Folder 27)
    - Legal, 1972 (Box 181, Folder 28)
    - Hospitals, General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 181, Folder 29)
    - Public Health, 1961-1969 (Box 181, Folder 30)
    - Public Welfare, 1961-1969 (Box 181, Folder 31)
    - Schools, University of Utah, Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 181, Folder 32)
    - Schools, Brigham Young University, Correspondence, 1956-1968 (Box 181, Folder 33)
    - Salt Lake City
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, PP of Utah from 1970
        - 1970-1972 (Box 181, Folder 34)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 181)
      - Affiliation, PP of Utah, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 181, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 181)
      - PP of Utah, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 181, Folder 36)
      - PP Association of Utah from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 181, Folder 37)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 181)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1970-1974 (Box 181, Folder 38)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965, INACTIVE, 1965 (Box 181, Folder 39)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1965, INACTIVE, 1965-1967 (Box 181, Folder 40)
      - PP Association from 1963, INACTIVE, 1963-1968 (Box 181, Folder 41)
      - Reports, Members from 1964, INACTIVE, 1964-1966 (Box 181, Folder 42)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips from 1964
      - 1964-1971 (Box 181, Folder 43)
      - 1978 (Box 181)
    - Salt Lake City & Ogden, Field Trips, 1961-1965 (Box 181, Folder 44)
  - Vermont
    - Contacts, 1963-1968 (Box 181, Folder 45)
    - Hospitals, 1963-1969 (Box 181, Folder 46)
    - Public Health, 1963-1969 (Box 181, Folder 47)
    - United Fund, United Community Fund, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 48)
    - Schools, General, 1963-1968 (Box 181, Folder 49)
    - University of Vermont, 1965-1971 (Box 181, Folder 50)
    - Burlington, Field Trips, 1965 (Box 181, Folder 51)
    - Brattleboro, PP, 1966-1968 (Box 181, Folder 52)
    - Burlington
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 181, Folder 53)
        - 1976, 1979 (Box 181)
      - Affiliation, PP Association of Vermont, Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1973 (Box 181, Folder 54)
        - 1976-1981 (Box 181)
      - PP Association of Vermont, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 181, Folder 55)
      - PP from 1964
        - 1965-1974 (Box 181, Folder 56)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 181)
      - PP Association of Vermont, Reports, General, 1965-1969 (Box 181, Folder 57)
      - PP Association of Vermont, Reports, Members from 1965
        - 1965-1972 (Box 181, Folder 58)
        - 1976 (Box 181)
      - PP League, Publicity, 1969 (Box 181, Folder 59)
    - Springfield, PP of Greater Springfield, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 60)
  - Virginia
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1971 (Box 181, Folder 61)
    - Contacts, 1956-1972 (Box 181, Folder 62)
    - Hospitals, The Fauquier, 1960-1967 (Box 181, Folder 63)
    - Legal, 1946-1974 (Box 181, Folder 64)
    - Migrant, 1962-1964 (Box 181, Folder 65)
    - Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 181, Folder 66)
    - Public Health, Correspondence from 1962
      - 1962-1973 (Box 181, Folder 67)
      - 1976 (Box 181)
    - Public Welfare, Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 181, Folder 68)
    - United Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 181, Folder 69)
    - Schools, General, 1958-1974 (Box 181, Folder 70)
    - University of, 1961-1966 (Box 181, Folder 71)
    - Association of Virginia, PP Affiliates, 1979 (Box 181, Folder 72)
    - Danville, Danville River Project, 1957-1959 (Box 181, Folder 73)
    - Hampton
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1975-1977 (Box 181, Folder 74)
      - Affiliation, Peninsula Planned Parenthood, 1976-1979 (Box 181, Folder 75)
      - Peninsula PP, Inc., Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 181, Folder 76)
      - Peninsula Planned Parenthood, 1976-1979 (Box 181, Folder 77)
    - Norfolk
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1974 (Box 181, Folder 78)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 181)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1965
        - 1965-1974 (Box 181, Folder 79)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 181)
      - PP of Tidewater Virginia, Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 181, Folder 80)
      - PP, 1966-1974 (Box 181, Folder 81)
      - PP, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1970 (Box 181, Folder 82)
      - Reports, Members, 1967-1972 (Box 181, Folder 83)
    - Richmond
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1946
        - 1946-1974 (Box 181, Folder 84)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 181)
      - Affiliation, PP League, Correspondence from 1959
        - 1959-1974 (Box 182, Folder 1)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 182)
      - Virginia League for PP, Legal (Eve Paul), 1978 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Virginia League for PP from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 3)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 182)
      - Virginia League for PP, 1967-1969 (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - PP League, 1965-1966 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - PP League, 1963-1964 (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Virginia League for PP, Chapters from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 7)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 182)
      - Field Visit, Derwent Suthers, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1963 (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - PP League 25th Anniversary, Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 5/10/63, 1962-1963 (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - PP League, Rotary Club, Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 4/62, 1961-1962 (Box 182, Folder 11)
      - PP League, Projects & Proposals, 1970 (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 182, Folder 13)
      - Reports, Members from 1964
        - 1964-1973 (Box 182, Folder 14)
        - 1975 (Box 182)
      - PP League, Virgina Academy Science & Public Health, First Virgina Population Conference, 1960-1970 (Box 182, Folder 15)
      - PP League, Publicity, Pamphlets, etc., 1955-1969 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Roanoke
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1976-1980 (Box 182, Folder 17)
      - Affiliation, PP Roanoke Valley, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 182, Folder 18)
      - PP Roanoke Valley, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 19)
      - PP PF Roanoke Valley, 1976-1979 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Southeast Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1964-1968 (Box 182, Folder 21)
  - Washington
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1964-1965 (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Contacts from 1965
      - 1965-1974 (Box 182, Folder 23)
      - 1975 (Box 182)
    - Department HEW, Region X, Family Planning Services from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 24)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 182)
    - Department of Licensing, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1979 (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Legal, 1942-1969 (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Migrant, 1963-1968 (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Public Health from 1961
      - 1961-1974 (Box 182, Folder 28)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 182)
    - Public Welfare, 1962-1965 (Box 182, Folder 29)
    - United Fund, 1969 (Box 182, Folder 30)
    - Schools, General, 1964-1969 (Box 182, Folder 31)
    - University of Washington, 1965-1969 (Box 182, Folder 32)
    - Bellingham
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1970-1973 (Box 182, Folder 33)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 182)
      - PP Affiliation, PPWP Washington, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 34)
      - Affiliation, PP Whatcom County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 182)
      - Family Planning Association of Whatcom County from 1970
        - 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
      - PP, Reports, Members, 1970-1972 (Box 182, Folder 37)
      - Field Visit, 1973 (Box 182, Folder 38)
    - Everett
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1970-1973 (Box 182, Folder 39)
        - 1975 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, PP Snohomish County, Correspondence from 1970
        - 1970-1973 (Box 182, Folder 40)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 182)
      - PP of Snohomish County from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 182, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 182)
      - PP of Snohomish County, Reports, Members, 1970-1972 (Box 182, Folder 42)
    - Kennewick
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1977-1980 (Box 182, Folder 43)
      - Affiliation, PP of Benton Franklin Counties, 1976-1979 (Box 182, Folder 44)
      - PP of Benton Franklin Counties, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 45)
    - Olympia, Affiliation, PP of Thurston County, 1979 (Box 182, Folder 46)
    - Seattle
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, Documents, 1975-1978 (Box 182, Folder 47)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1951-1972 (Box 182, Folder 48)
      - Affiliation, PP Seattle/ King County, Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 182, Folder 49)
      - Affiliation, PP Center, Correspondence, 1949-1974 (Box 182, Folder 50)
      - PP Seattle/King, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 182, Folder 51)
      - PP of Seattle/King County, 1975-1979 (Box 182, Folder 52)
      - PP Center, 1970-1974 (Box 182, Folder 53)
      - PP Center, 1968-1969 (Box 182, Folder 54)
      - PP Center, 1966-1967 (Box 182, Folder 55)
      - PP Center, 1964-1966 (Box 182, Folder 56)
      - Field Trips, 1953-1963 (Box 182, Folder 57)
      - Reports, Members, 1963-1970 (Box 182, Folder 58)
      - Reports, General, 1963-1969 (Box 182, Folder 59)
      - Dr. Guttmacher's Trip, 11/62, 1962-1963 (Box 182, Folder 60)
      - PP Center, Publicity, 1959-1975 (Box 182, Folder 61)
    - Spokane
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1971-1973 (Box 182, Folder 62)
        - 1976, 1979 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, Family Planning Association from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 63)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 182)
      - PP of Spokane, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 64)
      - PP, Spokane Family Planning Association from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 65)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 182, Folder 66)
      - PP Committee, 1964-1969 (Box 182, Folder 67)
      - Reports, Members, 1967-1968 (Box 182, Folder 68)
      - PP, Publicity, 1972 (Box 182, Folder 69)
      - PP, Reports, General, 1971 (Box 182, Folder 70)
      - Reports, Members, 1971-1972 (Box 182, Folder 71)
      - Field Trips, 1963-1969 (Box 182, Folder 72)
    - Tacoma
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws
        - 1973-1974 (Box 182, Folder 73)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, PP Pierce County from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 182, Folder 74)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 182)
      - PP Pierce County from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 182, Folder 75)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
      - PP Pierce County, Reports, Members, 1972 (Box 182, Folder 76)
    - Walla Walla
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1971
        - 1971-1973 (Box 182, Folder 77)
        - 1975, 1980 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 78)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
      - PP of Walla Walla, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1978 (Box 182, Folder 79)
      - Center for Family Planning from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 80)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
      - Reports, Members, 1971-1972 (Box 182, Folder 81)
    - Yakima
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1967
        - 1967-1972 (Box 182, Folder 82)
        - 1975 (Box 182)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1967
        - 1967-1973 (Box 182, Folder 83)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 182)
      - PP Association from 1966
        - 1966-1974 (Box 182, Folder 84)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
      - Reports, General, 1968-1971 (Box 182, Folder 85)
      - Reports, Members, 1968-1972 (Box 182, Folder 86)
    - Western Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1965-1973 (Box 182, Folder 87)
  - West Virginia
    - Anti-Poverty, 1966-1968 (Box 182, Folder 88)
    - Contacts from 1965
      - 1965-1974 (Box 182, Folder 89)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 182)
    - Hospitals, 1962-1965 (Box 182, Folder 90)
    - Legal, 1958-1970 (Box 182, Folder 91)
    - Migrants, 1962 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Public Health, 1956-1971 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Public Welfare, 1961-1972 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin Family Planning, Coordinating Council, 1971 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia
    - West Virginia Family Planning, Council, 1970 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Schools, General, 1953-1965 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - United Fund, United Community Services, 1967-1969 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - West Virginia University, 1964-1970 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Parkersburg
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1969
        - 1969-1974 (Box 183, Folder 9)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 183)
      - Affiliation, Correspondence from 1961
        - 1961-1974 (Box 183, Folder 10)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 183)
      - PP of Parkersburg, Trip Report, Andy Diaz, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 11)
      - PP Association from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 183, Folder 12)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 183)
      - PP Association, 1963-1967 (Box 183, Folder 13-14)
      - Field Trips, 1954-1965 (Box 183, Folder 15)
      - Reports, Clinics, 1958-1960 (Box 183, Folder 16)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1969 (Box 183, Folder 17)
      - Reports, Members from 1961
        - 1961-1972 (Box 183, Folder 18)
        - 1975 (Box 183)
      - Publicity, 1961-1967 (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Whitesville
      - Affiliation, Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 183, Folder 20)
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1966 (Box 183, Folder 21)
      - PP Boone/Raleigh City, 1962-1966 (Box 183, Folder 22)
      - Reports, General, 1964-1966 (Box 183, Folder 23)
      - Reports, Members, 1964-1966 (Box 183, Folder 24)
      - Field Trips, 1961-1964 (Box 183, Folder 25)
    - Clarksburg League for Service, 1964-1965 (Box 183, Folder 26)
    - Charleston, Field Trips, 1950-1969 (Box 183, Folder 27)
  - Wisconsin
    - Anti-Poverty Program, 1964-1966 (Box 183, Folder 28)
    - Contacts from 1965
      - 1965-1973 (Box 183, Folder 29)
      - 1976 (Box 183)
    - Hospitals, 1962-1968 (Box 183, Folder 30)
    - Legal, 1967-1968 (Box 183, Folder 31)
    - Migrants, 1956-1972 (Box 183, Folder 32)
    - (State) Public Health
      - 1958-1974 (Box 183, Folder 33)
      - 1975 (Box 183)
    - Public Welfare, 1964-1967 (Box 183, Folder 34)
    - Wisconsin Family Planning, Coordinating Council, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 35)
    - Schools, General from 1961
      - 1961-1969 (Box 183, Folder 36)
      - 1975 (Box 183)
    - Schools, University of Wisconsin, Correspondence from 1959 (empty) (Box 183, Folder 37)
    - Milwaukee
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1953
        - 1957-1972 (Box 183, Folder 38)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 183)
      - Affiliation, PP Association, Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1973 (Box 183, Folder 39)
        - 1976-1980 (Box 183)
      - PP Association of Wisconsin, Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-1979 (Box 183, Folder 40)
      - PP Association from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 183, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 183)
      - PP Association, 1966-1967 (Box 183, Folder 42)
      - PP Association, 1962-1965 (Box 183, Folder 43)
      - PP Association, 1961 (Box 183, Folder 44)
      - PP Association of Wisconsin, Chapters, 1976-1979 (Box 183, Folder 45)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1964 (Box 183, Folder 46)
      - PP Association, Reports, Clinics, 1959-1962 (Box 183, Folder 47)
      - PP Association, Reports, General, 1959-1971 (Box 183, Folder 48)
      - PP Association, Reports, Members, 1960-1973 (Box 183, Folder 49)
      - Publicity, 1963-1967 (Box 183, Folder 50)
  - Wyoming
    - Field Trips, 1960-1962 (Box 183, Folder 51)
    - Midwest Region, Reports, Field Trips, 1966 (Box 183, Folder 52)
    - Contacts from 1960
      - 1961-1974 (Box 183, Folder 53)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 183)
    - Hospitals, 1966 (Box 183, Folder 54)
    - Legal, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 55)
    - Migrants, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 56)
    - Public Health, 1961-1971 (Box 183, Folder 57)
    - Public Welfare, 1961-1970 (Box 183, Folder 58)
    - Schools, General, 1965 (Box 183, Folder 59)
    - PP Committee, Publicity, 1961 (Box 183, Folder 60)
    - Cheyenne, PP Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 183, Folder 61)
  - New York, New York
    - PPNYC
      - City Family Planning Information Service, 1971-1973 (Box 183, Folder 62)
      - Margaret Sanger Center from 1973
        - 1972-1974 (Box 183, Folder 63)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 183)
      - 22nd St. Center, 1972-1973 (Box 183, Folder 64)
      - Family Planning Resources Center, 1969-1972 (Box 183, Folder 65)
    - PPNYC & PPWP, First National Workshop: Planning & Providing Abortion Services, 9/20-24/72, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 66)
    - PPNYC, Members, Manual, 9/67, 1967 (Box 183, Folder 67)
    - Planned Parenthood Issues Manual: "What It Is and How to Use It, circa 1979 (Box 183, Folder 68)
    - Merger, 1964-1965 (Box 183, Folder 69)
    - Planned Parenthood, Merger: Manhattan and the Bronx, 1965-1969 (Box 183, Folder 70)
    - Field Trips, 1956-1964 (Box 183, Folder 71)
    - Affiliation, Bronx PP Center, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws, 1947-1953 (Box 183, Folder 72)
    - PP Manhattan & Bronx, 1962-1965 (Box 183, Folder 73)
    - Bronx PP Center, 1961-1969 (Box 183, Folder 74)
    - Chelsea, Committee for Family Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 183, Folder 75)
    - Workbook on Planning and Providing Abortion Services, 5/1973 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Sanger Bureau
      - Articles of Association and Bylaws, 1963 (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Financial Arrangements, 1962-1973 (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - History, Various Dates, 1927-1970 (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Reports, Members, 1961-1970 (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Literature, Various Dates, 1958-1965 (Box 184, Folder 6)
      - Field Trips, 1952-1956 (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 184, Folder 8-11)
      - Agency for International Development, Second Annual Report, 7/1972 (Box 184, Folder 12)
      - Margaret, Sanger Bureau, 1967 (Box 184, Folder 13)
      - Reports, General, 1961-1967 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Hannah Stone PP Center, 1955-1966 (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Judson Health Center, 1962-1968 (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - University Settlement, 1960-1966 (Box 184, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut
    - Anti-Poverty, 1965-1967 (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - Clinics, General, 1964 (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Contacts, 1963-1969 (Box 184, Folder 20)
    - Hospitals, General from 1963
      - 1963-1966 (Box 184, Folder 21)
      - 1979 (Box 184)
    - Abortion, Legal, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 22)
    - Birth Control Situation
      - Legal, Briefs, Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 184, Folder 23)
      - Legal, Briefs, Griswold & Buxton, 1964-1965 (Box 184, Folder 24)
      - Legal, Correspondence, 1955-1968 (Box 184, Folder 25-27)
      - Legal, Briefs, 1958-1964 (Box 184, Folder 28-31)
      - Legal, Petition for Dr. Buxton, 1960 (Box 184, Folder 32)
      - Legal, Briefs, 1960 (Box 184, Folder 33)
      - Legal, Supreme Court Justices' Case Opinions, 10/60, 1960-1964 (Box 184, Folder 34)
      - Legal, Briefs, 1959 (Box 184, Folder 35)
    - Birth Control Plan, Legal, for Connecticut Pioneering Sunnen, 1956-1957 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Birth Control Situation, Legal, Publicity, News Clips, 1958-1964 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Legal, Lower Court, Demurrer, 1961 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Public Health, 1959-1968 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Projects, 1970 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Public Welfare, 1968 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Schools, General, Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - University of Connecticut, Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Yale University, Correspondence, 1958-1969 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Hartford, Field Trips, 1957-1963 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - New Haven
      - Field Trips, 1954-1962 (Box 185, Folder 11)
      - PP League, Reports, Members, 1962-1970 (Box 185, Folder 12)
      - PP League, Reports, General from 1958
        - 1958-1969 (Box 185, Folder 13)
        - 1975 (Box 185)
      - PP League, Public Affairs, 1977 (Box 185, Folder 14)
      - PP League, Publicity from 1957
        - 1963-1976 (Box 185, Folder 15)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 185)
      - PP Connecticut & Portchester, New York, Controversy Conference, 1/8/63, 1963-1969 (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - Hartford, PP League, 1962-1972 (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - New Haven
      - Affiliation, Audits, Budgets, Bylaws from 1947
        - 1947-1972 (Box 185, Folder 18)
        - 1976 (Box 185)
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957